<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Manuelrage.dev</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Manuelrage.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.129.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:02:23 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How a Stupid Bot Could Win Me Money</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-a-stupid-bot-could-win-me-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:02:23 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-a-stupid-bot-could-win-me-money/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am Elon Musk, I am weird.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/who-am-i-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:01:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/who-am-i-copy/</guid>
      <description>I was born and raised in South Africa, and later moved to the United States with a vision that would redefine entire industries. My relentless drive and innovative spirit led me to co-found companies like Zip2 and X.com, which eventually became PayPal. However, my most notable ventures are Tesla and SpaceX, where I&amp;rsquo;m pushing the boundaries of what&amp;rsquo;s possible in electric vehicles and space travel.
In a little over two decades, I&amp;rsquo;ve transformed from an ambitious entrepreneur into a household name, synonymous with groundbreaking technology and ambitious goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The illusion of innovation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/making-money-in-a-sad-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:01:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/making-money-in-a-sad-way/</guid>
      <description>I want to place a big disclaimer here: everything you are about to read does not refer to every company or startup you can think of, but still, 80% of them will probably fall into my negative perception.
As a software engineer, I&amp;rsquo;m fortunate to work in a field that&amp;rsquo;s both lucrative and in high demand. Or am I just dreaming?
It&amp;rsquo;s a profession that not only sustains me but also thrusts me into the very heart of the digital gold rush.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Am I</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:01:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is [Your Name]. I am currently studying reverse engineering for legal purposes and learning English. My focus area is binary exploitation.
Background I have a keen interest in understanding how software works at a fundamental level. This has led me to explore reverse engineering, where I dismantle software to see how it functions internally. This process is fascinating and helps in improving my problem-solving skills.
Interests Reverse Engineering: Delving into software internals to understand its workings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My New Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-new-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:59:14 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-new-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
